https://www.premosys.de/en/privacy-policy/

Privacy policy
I. Name and address of the controllerThe responsible entity in the context of the GDPR, other data protection laws applicable in the Member States of the European Union and other regulations of a data protection nature is:
Premosys GmbHHillstraﬂe 1454570 Kalenborn-ScheuernGermanyTel.: +49 6591/98311-0Fax.: +49 6591/98311-10E-Mail:Website: www.premosys.com1. Extent of the processing of personal dataWe process personal data of our users only to the extent that this is necessary for providing a functional website and our content and services. Processing of personal data of our users is performed routinely only with the consent of the user. An exception to this rule applies in cases where prior obtaining of consent is not possible on factual grounds and processing of the data is legally permitted.†2. Legal basis for processing personal dataInsofar as we obtain consent from the data subject to process personal data, Art. 6 Par. 1 a) GDPR serves as the legal basis.†When processing personal data is necessary for the performance of a contract whose contractual party is the data subject, Art. 6 Par. 1 b) GDPR is the legal basis. This applies as well for processing which is necessary for pre-contractual actions.†When processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which our company is subject, Art. 6 Par. 1 c) GDPR is the legal basis.†When processing is necessary in order to protect the vital interests of the data subject or of another natural person, Art. 6 Par. 1 d) GDPR serves as the legal basis.†When processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by our company or by a third party and where such interests are not overridden by the interests or fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject which require protection of personal data, Art. 6 Par. 1 f) GDPR serves as the legal basis.† †3. Data deletion and storage period The personal data of the data subject shall be deleted or blocked as soon as the purpose of the storage no longer applies. Storage beyond this time may occur if this has been provided for by the European or national legal body in Union law, laws or other regulations to which the controller is subject. The data are also blocked or deleted if a storage period prescribed by the named standards has expired unless there is a necessity for further storage of the data for entering into a contract or performance of a contract.††II: Provision of the Website and Creation of Log Files1. Description and scope of data processingEach time the web page is opened by a person or automated system a series of general data and information is generated.The following data are hereby collected:The browser types and versions usedThe operating system of the userThe Internet Service Provider of the userThe IP address of the userDate and time of the accessThe data are also stored in the log files of our system. Not affected by this are the IP addresses of the user or other data which enable associating of the data with a user. These data together with other personal data of the user are not stored.††2. Legal basis for processing:The legal basis for temporary storage of the data is Art. 6 Par. 1 f) GDPR.†3. Purpose of data processingTemporary storage of the IP address by the system is necessary in order to enable delivery of the website to the userís computer. This requires the IP address of the user to be stored for the duration of the session.†These purposes also apply to our legitimate interest in data processing pursuant to Art. 6 Par. 1 f) GDPR.†4. Storage duration The data are deleted as soon as their collection is no longer necessary for achievement of the purpose. When collection of the data is used for providing the website, this is the case when the respective session is ended.†5. Objection and elimination Collection of the data in order to provide the website and storage of the data in log files is absolutely necessary for operation of the Internet site. Consequently the user has no recourse to objection.† †III. Contact Form and E-Mail Contact1. Description and scope of data processing Our Internet site contains a contact form which can be used for making electronic contact. If a user makes use of this, the data entered by the user are transmitted to us and stored. These data are:†The given name of the userThe given e-mail address of the userThe given company nameThe message entered by the userAt the moment the message is sent the following data are also stored:†The given name of the userThe given e-mail address of the userThe given company nameThe message entered by the userTo process the data your consent is obtained as part of the sending procedure and you are referred to this Privacy Statement.†Alternately you may contact us using the e-mail address provided. In this case the userís personal data transmitted with the e-mail are stored.† In this context no data are shared with a third party. The data are used solely for processing the conversation.†2. Legal basis for processingWhen there is consent from the user, the legal basis for processing is Art. 6 Par. 1 a) GDPR.†The legal basis for processing the data which is conveyed as part of sending an e-mail is Art. 6 Par. 1 f) GDPR. If the e-mail contact is for the purpose of entering into a contract, Art. 6 Par. 1 b) GDPR represents an additional legal basis.†3. Purpose of the data processingWe process the personal data from the entry screen solely in order to facilitate the contact. When contact is by e-mail the necessary and legitimate interest in processing of the data applies.†The other personal data processes during sending are used to prevent misuse of the contact form and to ensure the security of our IT systems.†4. Storage duration The data are deleted as soon as they are no longer needed for achieving the purpose of their gathering. For the personal data from the entry screen of the contact form and those sent via e-mail, this is the case when the respective conversation with the user is ended. The conversation is ended when it is apparent from the circumstances that the matter is question has been finally resolved.†5. Objection and eliminationThe user may at any time rescind his consent to process his or her personal data. If the user contacts us by e-mail, he or she may object to the storage of his or her personal dat4a at any time. In such cases the conversation cannot be continued.†All personal data which were stored in connection with contact initiation are then deleted.†IV. Rights of the Data Subject If your personal data are processed, then you are a data subject pursuant to GDPR and have the following rights with respect to the controller:†1. Right of access You may obtain confirmation as to whether or not personal data concerning you have been processed by us.†If such processing has taken place, you have the right to the following information:†(1)† The purposes of the processing;(2)† The envisaged period for which the personal data will be stored or, if not possible, the criteria used to determine that period;(3)† The right to request from the controller rectification or erasure of your personal data or restriction of processing of personal data or to object to such processing;(4)† The right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority; You have the right to demand to know whether your personal data have been transferred to a third country or to an international organization, and you have the right to be informed of the appropriate safeguards pursuant to Art. 46 GDPR.†2. Right to rectification You have a right to obtain rectification and/or supplementation from the controller for processed personal data which pertains to you when it is inaccurate or incomplete. The controller shall perform the rectification without delay.†3. Right to erasurea) Erasure obligationYou have the right to obtain from the controller the erasure of personal data concerning you without undue delay and the controller has the obligation to erase personal data without undue delay where one of the following grounds applies:(1)† The personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed.(2)† You withdraw consent on which the processing is based according to (a) of Art. 6 Par. 1 or (a) of Art. 9 Par. 2, and where there is no other legal ground for the processing.(3)† You object to the processing pursuant to Art. 21 Par. 1 GDPR and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing, or you object to the processing pursuant to Art. 21 Par. 2 GDPR.†(4)† Your personal data have been unlawfully processed.(5)† Your personal data must be erased for compliance with a legal obligation in Union or Member State law to which the controller is subject.(6)† Your personal data have been collected in relation to the offer of information society services referred to in Art. 8 Par. 1 GDPR.b) Information to third parties If the controller has made your personal data public and is obligated pursuant to Art. 17 Part. 1 GDPR to erase these data, then he shall take all appropriate measures subject to the available technology and the implementation costs, including of a technical nature, to inform controllers who process the personal data that you as data subject have demanded erasure of all links to these personal data or of copies or replications of this personal data.†c) ExceptionsThe right to erasure shall not apply to the extent that processing is necessary(1)† for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information;(2)† for compliance with a legal obligation which requires processing by Union or Member State law to which the controller is subject or for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller;(3)† for reasons of public interest in the area of public health in accordance with points (h) and (i) of† Art.†9 Par.†2 (h) and (i) as well as Art.†9 Par.†3 GDPR;(4)† for archiving purposes in the public interest, scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes in accordance with Article 89 Par. 1 in so far as the right referred to in paragraph 1 is likely to render impossible or seriously impair the achievement of the objectives of that processing, or(5)† for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.4. Right to object You have the right to object, on grounds relating to his or her particular situation, at any time to processing of your personal data which is based on Art. 6 Par. 1 point e or f GDPR, including profiling based on those provisions. We will no longer process the personal data unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override the interests, rights and freedoms of the data subject or for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims. Where your personal data are processed for direct marketing purposes, you have the right to object at any time to processing of your personal data for such marketing, which includes profiling to the extent that it is related to such direct marketing. Where you object to processing for direct marketing purposes, the personal data shall no longer be processed for such purposes. In the context of the use of information society services, and notwithstanding Directive 2002/58/EC, you may exercise your right to object by automated means using technical specifications.5. Right to withdraw consent You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing consent does not affect the legality of the processing performed between the time of consent and withdrawal of consent.†6. Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority Without prejudice to any other administrative or judicial remedy, you shall have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of your habitual residence, place of work or place of the alleged infringement if you consider that the processing of your personal data infringes this Regulation. The supervisory authority with which the complaint has been lodged shall inform the complainant on the progress and the outcome of the complaint including the possibility of a judicial remedy pursuant to†Art.†78 GDPR.V. Google AnalyticsThis website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google LLC ("Google"). The use includes the operating mode "Universal Analytics". This makes it possible to assign data, sessions and interactions across multiple devices to a pseudonymous user ID, thus analyzing the activities of a user across devices. This privacy policy is provided by www.intersoft-consulting.de.
Google Analytics uses so-called "cookies", text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of the use of the website by you. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. However, in the event of activation of IP anonymisation on this website, your IP address will be shortened beforehand by Google within member states of the European Union or in other contracting states of the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be sent to a Google server in the US and shortened there. We point out that on this website Google Analytics has been extended by an IP anonymization to ensure an anonymous collection of IP addresses (so-called IP masking). The IP address provided by Google Analytics as part of Google Analytics will not be merged with other Google data. For more information about Terms of Use and Privacy, please visit www.google.com/analytics/terms/en.html or visit policies.google.com.PURPOSES OF PROCESSING
On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide other services related to website activity and internet usage to the website operator.LEGAL BASIS
The legal basis for the use of Google Analytics is your consent in accordance with Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. a DSGVO (https://dsgvo-gesetz.de/art-6-dsgvo/).RECIPIENTS / CATEGORIES OF RECIPIENTS
The recipient of the data collected is Google.TRANSMISSION IN THIRD STATES
The personal data will be transmitted under the EU-US Privacy Shield on the basis of the adequacy decision of the European Commission in the USA. You can get the certificate here (https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI).DURATION OF DATA STORAGE
The data sent by us and linked to cookies, user IDs (eg user ID) or advertising IDs will be automatically deleted after 14 months. The deletion of data whose retention period has been reached is done automatically once a month.AFFECTED RIGHTS
You can revoke your consent at any time with future effect by preventing the storage of cookies by setting your browser software accordingly; however, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use all the features of this website to the fullest extent possible.
In addition, you may prevent the collection of the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website (including your IP address) to Google and the processing of this data by Google by using the browser add-on (https: / /tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) to download and install. Opt-out cookies prevent future collection of your data when you visit this website. To prevent Universal Analytics tracking across devices, you must opt-out on all systems you use. If you click here, the opt-out cookie will be set: Disable Google Analytics
Do you have anymore questions?
Contact us!
About Cookies
This website uses cookies. Those have two functions: On the one hand they are providing basic functionality for this website. On the other hand they allow us to improve our content for you by saving and analyzing anonymized user data. You can redraw your consent to using these cookies at any time. Find more information regarding cookies on our Data Protection Declaration and regarding us on the Imprint.
Settings
Mandatory
These cookies are needed for a smooth operation of our website.
Name
Purpose
Lifetime
Type
Provider
CookieConsent
Saves your consent to using cookies.
1
year
HTML
Website
fe_typo_user
Assigns your browser to a session on the server.
session
HTTP
Website
Marketing
With the help of these cookies we strive to improve our offer for our users. By means of anonymized data of website users we can optimize the user flow. This enables us to improve ads and website content.
Name
Purpose
Lifetime
Type
Provider
_pk_id
Used to store a few details about the user such as the unique visitor ID.
13
months
HTML
Matomo
_pk_ref
Used to store the attribution information, the referrer initially used to visit the website.
6
months
HTML
Matomo
_pk_ses
Short lived cookie used to temporarily store data for the visit.
30
minutes
HTML
Matomo
_pk_cvar
Short lived cookie used to temporarily store data for the visit.
30
minutes
HTML
Matomo
_pk_hsr
Short lived cookie used to temporarily store data for the visit.
30
minutes
HTML
Matomo
_ga
Used to distinguish users.
2
years
HTML
Google
_gat
Used to throttle request rate.
1
day
HTML
Google
_gid
Used to distinguish users.
1
day
HTML
Google
_ga_--container-id--
Persists session state.
2
years
HTML
Google
_gac_--property-id--
Contains campaign related information for the user. If you have linked your Google Analytics and Google Ads accounts, Google Ads website conversion tags will read this cookie unless you opt-out.
3
months
HTML
Google
_gcl_au
Used by Google AdSense to experiment with advertisement efficiency.
3
months
HTML
Google
AMP_TOKEN
Contains a token that can be used to retrieve a Client ID from AMP Client ID service. Other possible values indicate opt-out, inflight request or an error retrieving a Client ID from AMP Client ID service.
1
year
HTML
Google
_dc_gtm_--property-id--
Used by DoubleClick (Google Tag Manager) to help identify the visitors by either age, gender or interests.
Used as unique user identifier. The cookie allows user tracking across many Microsoft domains.
Saves anonymous user data from multiple website visits on multiple sites to test advertisement efficiency.
Stores the unique visitor ID.
If JavaScript is not enabled, this pixel initiates a connection to facebook.
